const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Who are the Aboriginal peoples of Canada?",
    options: ["The first European settlers to arrive in Canada", "The descendents of the first Australian immigrants to Canada", "The first people to live in Canada", "The first settlers of Newfoundland"],
    answer: "The first people to live in Canada"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What are the three main groups of Aboriginal peoples?",
    options: ["First Nations, Métis and Inuit", "Acadians, Métis and Inuit", "United Empire Loyalists, Métis and Inuit", "Inuit, Métis and Acadians"],
    answer: "First Nations, Métis and Inuit"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Who are the Métis?",
    options: ["The distinct aboriginal people of Atlantic Canada", "A people of mixed Inuit/FirstNations ancestry most of who live on the Prairies", "First Nations people speaking the Michif dialect", "A distinct people of mixed Aboriginal and European ancestry"],
    answer: "A distinct people of mixed Aboriginal and European ancestry"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Who were the United Empire Loyalists?",
    options: ["Settlers who came to Canada from the United States during the American Revolution", "Aboriginal peoples", "Métis", "Inuit"],
    answer: "Settlers who came to Canada from the United States during the American Revolution"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What does Confederation mean?",
    options: ["The United States Confederate soldiers came to Canada", "Joining of communities to become a province", "Joining of suburbs to form a large city", "Joining of provinces to make a new country"],
    answer: "Joining of provinces to make a new country"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is the name of the Royal Anthem of Canada?",
    options: ["O Canada", "God Save the Queen (or King)", "La Marseillaise", "The Star-Spangled Banner"],
    answer: "God Save the Queen (or King)"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What year was Confederation?",
    options: ["1867", "1871", "1898", "1864"],
    answer: "1867"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "When did the British North America Act come into effect?",
    options: ["1871", "1898", "1867", "1905"],
    answer: "1867"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which province was split into two at Confederation?",
    options: ["Lower Canada", "Newfoundland", "Upper Canada", "The Province of Canada"],
    answer: "The Province of Canada"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Which was the last province to join Canada?",
    options: ["Newfoundland", "Alberta", "Saskatchewan", "British Columbia"],
    answer: "Newfoundland"
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "When is Canada Day and what does it celebrate?",
    options: ["June 15th of each year to celebrate the anniversary of Confederation", "August 8th of each year to celebrate the joining of British Columbia to Confederation", "July 1st of each year to celebrate the anniversary of Confederation", "May 21st of each year to remember Queen Victoria"],
    answer: "July 1st of each year to celebrate the anniversary of Confederation"
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Who was the first Prime Minister of Canada?",
    options: ["Louis Riel", "Sir John A. Macdonald", "Lester B. Pearson", "Abraham Lincoln"],
    answer: "Sir John A. Macdonald"
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "What part of the Constitution legally protects the basic rights and freedoms of all Canadians?",
    options: ["The British Charter of Rights and Freedoms", "The Canadian Charter of Rights", "The Canadian Charter of Freedoms", "The Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms"],
    answer: "The Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms"
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "When did the Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms become part of the Canadian Constitution?",
    options: ["1867", "1905", "1982", "1878"],
    answer: "1982"
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "Name two fundamental freedoms protected by the Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms?",
    options: ["Freedom of conscience and religion, and Freedom of association", "Equality rights, and to care for Canada's heritage", "Basic freedoms, and obeying laws", "Aboriginal peoples' rights, and to volunteer"],
    answer: "Freedom of conscience and religion, and Freedom of association"
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "Name three additional rights protected by the Canadian Charter of Rights and Freedoms?",
    options: ["Freedom of speech, Right to own land, and Right to a fair trial", "Mobility rights, Multiculturalism, and Aboriginal Peoples' rights", "Right to ski anywhere in Canada, Moving rights, and Right to public assembly", "Right to vote, Right to speak publicly, and Security rights"],
    answer: "Mobility rights, Multiculturalism, and Aboriginal Peoples' rights"
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "What is the meaning of the Remembrance Day poppy?",
    options: ["To remember our Soverign, Queen Elizabeth II", "To celebrate Confederation", "To honour Prime Ministers who have died", "To remember the sacrifice of Canadians who have served or died in wars up to the present day"],
    answer: "To remember the sacrifice of Canadians who have served or died in wars up to the present day"
  }
]

export default questions